Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Historical Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Research files
  - McLaughlin, Frank, Primary Care Judgements of Nurses and Physicians, Volumes 1, 2, and 3, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 925-927)
  - McLemore, S. Dale, and Richard J. Hill, "Management-Training Effectiveness: A Study of Nurse Managers," Bureau of Business Research, University of Texas, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 928)
  - McPartland, Thomas, "Formal Education and the Process of Professionalization: A Study of Student Nurses," Community Studies, Inc., Kansas City, Missouri, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 929)
  - Mednick, Sarnoff A., "The Preschizophrenic," University of Michigan and Psychiatric Institute of Copenhagen, Denmark, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 930)
  - Merchant, Kathy, "Priorities Study," United Way of Greater New Haven, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 933)
  - Mickey, Janice, "Study of Extra-Hospital Nursing Needs, Manual of Instructions for Interviewers," Johns Hopkins University and Butler County Health Department, Circa 1958 (Box 80, Folder 934)
  - Minnesota, University of (Martinson, Ida M.), "Faculty Research", 1979 (Box 80, Folder 935)
  - Mishler, Elliot G., and Nancy E. Waxler, "Interaction in Families with Schizophrenia: An Experimental Study," Harvard Medical School, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 936)
  - Moore, Lucille, and George D. White, "Report of the University of Texas School of Nursing Study: Teaching Processes in Maternal and Infant Care", 1964 (Box 80, Folder 937)
  - Morgan, Jean, "A Study of an Extendor Role for Professional Nurses," Central Wisconsin Colony and Training School, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 938)
  - Mount Sinai Hospital, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, "Home Care Program Report," 1963-1964, Circa 1964 (Box 81, Folder 940)
  - Mulreany, Robert, Clifton Phalen, et al., A Survey of Tuberculosis Patients in the South Bronx, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 941)
  - National Center for Health Services Research
    - Brook, Robert H., "Quality of Medical Care Assessment Using Outcome Measures", 1977 (Box 81, Folder 944)
    - Corman, John, "Nurse Practitioners and Physician Assistants, A Research Agenda", 1978 (Box 81, Folder 945)
    - Johns Hopkins, "Developing a Quality Assurance Strategy for Primary Care", 1980 (Box 81, Folder 946)
    - Michigan, University of, "Needed Research in the Assessment and Monitoring of the Quality of Medical Care", 1978 (Box 81, Folder 947)
    - System Sciences, Inc., "Nurse Practitioner and Physician Assistant Training and Deployment", 1977 (Box 81, Folder 948)
  - National Institute of Mental Health
    - "Region III Conference on Planning In-Service Training Programs in Mental Health," Baltimore, Maryland, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 949)
    - "State and Local Summaries: Psychiatric and Mental Health Nursing Activities", 1965 (Box 82, Folder 950)
    - "Utilization of Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing Research for Improvement of Patient Care," Region IV, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 951)
  - National Technical Information Service, "Study of Nurse Practitioner Programs, Students, Graduates, and Employers of Nurse Practitioners," State University of New York at Buffalo, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 952-953)
  - New, Per Kong-ming, Nursing Research Conference, Report, Community Studies, Inc., 1957 (Box 82, Folder 954)
  - Nickerson, Irma W., "First Annual Report: Pilot Floor, Moffitt Hospital," University of California Medical Center, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 956)
  - Nite, Gladys, "A Working Philosophy of Nursing Care," Community Studies, Inc., Kansas City, Missouri, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 957)
  - Nursing Science articles, by J. Berthold, M. Brown, G. Carter, I. King, H. Peplau, P. Putnam, M. Rogers, and J. Taylor, 1963-1965 (Box 82, Folder 958)
  - Oklahoma, University of, "Proceedings: Planning for Comprehensive In-Service Training in a State Mental Health Program", 1963 (Box 83, Folder 959)
  - Oxaal, Ivar, Social Stratification and Personnel Turnover in the Hospital, Ohio State University, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 960)
  - Pair, Nona Tiller, and Jo Eleanor Elliott, One Road Toward Adequate Nursing Service, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 961)
  - Palmer, Mary Ellen, Self Evaluation of Nursing Performance Based on Clinical Practice Objectives, Boston University Press, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 962)
  - Parks, John, "Nursing in Maternity and Newborn Care," Final Report (First Draft), George Washington University Hospital, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 963)
  - Perker, Nora I., and Judith A. Humphreys, "Survey of Graduates of the University of Toronto Baccalaureate Course in Nursing," III, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 964)
  - Pitel, Martha, "Study of a More Active Use of Nursing Personnel in Ambulatory Patient Care," University of Kansas Medical School, Undated (Box 83, Folder 965)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, Report of Work Conference: Graduate Education in Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 966)
  - Plaas, Hyram, et al., The Evaluation of Policy-Related Research in Emergency Medical Services, Volumes I-IV, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 967-970)
  - Posman, Harry, Continuity in Care for Impaired Older Persons, Committee on Health, Department of Public Affairs, New York, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 975)
  - Powell, Frances D., "Nursing as Professional Support: A Functional Analysis," Department of Sociology, Boston College, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 976)
  - Redmond, Mary M., Training for Clinical Research in Psychiatric-Mental Health Nursing, School of Nursing, Catholic University of America, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 977)
  - Reichman, Walter, "Group Problem Solving Under Restrained Communication as a Function of Problem Presentation and Information," Baruch School, City University of New York, Undated (Box 85, Folder 978)
  - Reissman, Leonard, and Ralph V. Platou, "The Motivation and Socialization of Medical Students," Tulane University, Undated (Box 85, Folder 979)
  - Reiter, Frances, "Quality of Nursing Care: A Report of a Field-Study to Establish Criteria, 1950-1954" (Box 85, Folder 980)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, A Survey of Manuscript Sources for the History of Nursing and Nursing Education in the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 983)
  - Rogers, Edna L., Measurement of Status Relations in a Hospital, Ohio State University, 1959 (Box 85, Folder 984)
  - Rosenfeld, Leonard S., "Ambulatory Care: Planning and Organization," Health and Hospital Planning Council of Southern New York Incorporated, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 985)
  - Rubin, Reva, "Definitions in Nursing Therapy," paper presented at Conference on Maternal and Child Nursing, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 986)
  - Rush University, Research Report, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 987)
  - Sadler, Alfred, and Blair Sadler, "First Progress Report of the Yale Trauma Program," Yale University School of Nursing, Department of Surgery, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 988)
  - Safford, Beverly J., "A Study of Personnel Utilization at Lapeer State Home," Michigan Department of Health, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 989)
  - Sasmor, Jeannette, "The National Survey of State Boards of Medicine and State Boards of Nursing Perceptions of the Role and Functions of Primary Care Nurse Practitioners", 1982 (Box 86, Folder 990)
  - Saunders, Cicely, "The Moment of Truth: Some Aspects of the Care of the Dying Patient," lecture, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 991)
  - Schlotfeldt, Rozella M., Creating a Climate for Nursing Research, Case Western Reserve University, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 992)
  - Schwartz, Doris, "Nursing Needs of the Chronically Ill Ambulatory Patient," working papers, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 993)
  - Shagass, C., "Evoked Response Studies of Central Excitability in Psychiatric Disorders," Temple University Medical Center, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 994)
  - Shalit, Pearl R., "Annual State Summary: Psychiatric and Mental Health Nursing Activities," USDHEW, Public Health Service, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 995)
  - Sherrick, Anna Pearl, "Montana High School Counselors' Concepts of Professional Nursing," Montana State College, Bozeman, Montana, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 996)
  - Shyne, Ann W., "Serving the Maternity Patient Through Family-Centered Public Health Nursing," Department of Public Affairs, New York, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 997)
  - Simms, Laura, "The Hospital Staff Nurse Position as Viewed by Baccalaureate Graduates in Nursing," Ph.D. dissertation, Columbia University, Teachers College, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 998)
  - Simonton, O. Carl, "The Psychological Causes and the Psychological Treatment of Cancer", 1978 (Box 87, Folder 1001)
  - Slater, Doris, "The Slater Nursing Competencies Rating Scale," Wayne State University, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 1002)
  - Smith, Alice E., "Faculty Research Development Project," Summary Progress Report, Columbia Union College, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 1003)
  - Smith, Gene M., "The Role of Personality in Nursing Education: A Comparison of Successful and Unsuccessful Student Nurses," pre-publication copy, Undated (Box 87, Folder 1005)
  - Smith, Helen C., "Progress Report for Training Project: Developing Teaching Techniques Designed to Improve Utilization of Knowledge from the General Education Component," University of Evansville, Indiana, Circa 1967-1969 (Box 87, Folder 1006)
  - Smith, Joyce G., "An Investigation of Interruptions in Nursing Care," Final Report, Montefiore Hospital, New York, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 1007)
  - Smith, Louise C., Factors Influencing Continuity of Nursing Service, Columbia University Teachers College, National League for Nursing sponsored, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 1008)
  - Snoke, Parnie S., and E. Richard Weinerman, "Yale Studies in Ambulatory Medical Care, IV. Comprehensive Care Programs in University Medical Centers", Undated (Box 87, Folder 1009)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, Kenneth Huggins, Nursing Education in the South, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 1010)
  - "Southern West Virginia Appalachian Regional Demonstration Health Program", 1967 (Box 88, Folder 1011)
  - Southwick, Wayne O., "Rehabilitation of Elderly Patients Having Hip Surgery," Progress Report, Yale University School of Medicine, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 1012)
  - Spitzer, Walter O., et al., "A Strategy for Evaluation of New Health Professionals," John E. Fogary International Center, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 1013)
  - Spring, Faye E., Man: A Holistic Conception for Nursing, Pilot Final Project Report, Frances Payne Bolton School of Nursing, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 1014)
  - Spurgeon, Roberta, "Analysis of the Verbal Communication of a Nurse with Three Autistic Children," Boston School of Nursing, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 1015)
  - Stanford University Medical Center, Nursing Research, Abstracts, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 1016)
  - Stein, Millicent, "A Measure of Nursing Performance Designed for Graduates of the Basic Program," University of California, Los Angeles, School of Nursing, Undated (Box 88, Folder 1017)
  - Stern, John A., "Role Differentials and Nursing Ideology," research proposal, Medical Care Research Center, Washington University, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 1018)
  - Stobo, Elizabeth, "Conference Report on the Educational Preparation of the Nurse for School Health Work," Columbia University, Teachers College, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 1019)
  - Storms, Doris M., and Margaret G. Arnstein, "Experimental Training Program for Nurse Practitioners," Final Report, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1020)
  - Taylor, Calvin, et al., Selection and Recruitment of Nurses and Nursing Students, University of Utah Press, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 1021)
  - Teal, Gilbert, "Causes of Student Withdrawal from Nurse Training," Final Report, Public Service Research, Inc., 1961 (Box 89, Folder 1022)
  - Thompson, John D., "A Study of a Postoperative Recovery Room and a Postanesthesia Recovery Room," Yale LEPH, 1957 (Box 89, Folder 1024)
  - Thrush, Randolph S., and Richard R. Lanese, "Hospital-Patient Communication: Parts I and II," Ohio State University, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 1025)
  - Thurston, John R., "The Relationship of Personality to Achievement in Nursing Education," Wisconsin State University, 1964 (Box 89, Folder 1026)
  - Torrance, Jane Taylor, "Children's Reactions to Intramuscular Injections: A Comparative Study of Needle and Jet Injections," University Medical Center, Cleveland, Ohio, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1027)
  - Tracy, Margaret, time study information, 1928, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 1028)
  - Trail, Ira D., and Jean E. Wold, "Toward Understanding Problems in Nursing through a Comparative Study of Personality Characteristics and Interpersonal Behaviors of Staff Nurses and Nurse Educators," University of California, Los Angeles, 1964 (Box 89, Folder 1029)
  - Trussell, Patricia, and Jennifer J. Carter, Registered Nurse Licensure Before/After a Baccalaureate Degree? University of Central Arkansas, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 1030)
  - Turner, R. Jay, "Social Structure and Crisis," Mental Health Research Unit, New York State Department of Mental Hygiene, New York, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 1033)
  - United States Department of Health and Human Services, National Institute of Mental Health, Proceedings: Psychiatric Mental Health Nursing Recruitment to the Specialty, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 1034)
  - VanBuskirk, Charles, Evaluation of an Experimental Nursing Curriculum, Final Report, Department of Patient Care Research, Presbyterian Hospital, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1035)
  - Vaughn, Sister Louise Marie, Attitudes of Nursing Students Toward Direct Patient Care, dissertation, Catholic University of America, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1036)
  - Vermont State Department of Mental Health, "Proceedings of a Technical Assistance Project Conference on Collaboration for Better Mental Health Services in Rural Communities", 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1037)
  - Veterans' Administration, Survey of Factors Relating to Job Satisfaction Among VA Nurses (1960 and 1970), 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1038)
  - Virginia State Department of Health, Appalachian Regional Health Demonstration Program, and appendices, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 1041-1042)
  - Visiting Nurse Service of New York, "Summary Report: Study of Psychological Needs of Aged Patients at Home", 1965 (Box 91, Folder 1043)
  - Washington, State of, "Project Report: Rehabilitation Education Service," 1959-1961, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 1048)
  - Washington, University of, Department of Health Services, "Sickness Impact Profile", 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 1049)
  - Wenner, Naomi K., and Mabel B. Cohen, "Emotional Aspects of Pregnancy," Final Report of Washington School of Psychiatry Project, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1050)
  - Werley, Harriet H., Walter Reed Army Medical Center, Report on Nursing Research Conference, 1959 (Box 92, Folder 1051)
  - Western Council on Higher Education for Nursing (WECHEN), Development of Personnel Toward Quality Nursing Care, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 1052)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education (WICHE), Newly Initiated and Completed Research, Volume 12, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 1053)
  - White, Opal, and Dorothy Bloch, et al., "Nursing in Community Mental Health Services", Undated (Box 93, Folder 1054)
  - White, Ruth P., Dana Quade, and Kerr L. White, "Patient Care Classification: Methods and Application, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 1055)
  - Whiting, J. Frank, The Nurse-Patient Relationship and the Healing Process, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 1056)
  - Wiens, Arthur N., "Conceptualization: A Step in Research," symposium, National League for Nursing Biennial Meeting, San Francisco, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 1057)
  - Wilson, Patience, and Maryann Pranulis, "Continuing Education Program for Public Health Nurses in Coronary Care," Project Report, 1970-1971, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 1058)
  - Wilson, Robert N., Coming Home: The Problem of After-Care, Southern Regional Education Board, Atlanta, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 1059)
  - Winstead-Fry, Patricia, "A Report to the Profession," Nursing Research Emphasis Grant for Doctoral Programs in Nursing, New York University, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 1060)
  - Wooldridge, Powhatan J., "A Demographic Study of Tuberculosis Mortality in Florida and the United States", 1960 (Box 93, Folder 1061)
  - "Working Group to Review the NCI/ACS Breast Cancer Detection Demonstration Projects, Report of the", 1977 (Box 94, Folder 1062)
  - Yale Trauma Program, "A Study and Analysis of Emergency Medical Services in Connecticut," Department of Surgery, Yale University, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 1063)
  - Yale University School of Medicine
    - "Cancer Center Grant Proposal", 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1064)
    - Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, "A Survey of Comprehensive Health Services in the Central Naugatuck Valley Region", 1970 (Box 94, Folder 1065)
    - Department of Surgery, "Second Progress Report of the Yale Trauma Program", 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1066)
    - L.E.P.H., "The Assessment of Patients for a Continuing Care Unit at Yale-New Haven Hospital", 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1067)
    - Office of Regional Activities and Continuing Education, "Medical Technology Programs in Connecticut: Patterns of Employment and Migration of Recent Graduates", 1975 (Box 94, Folder 1068)
  - Yale University School of Nursing, "Career Profile and Curriculum Evaluation", 1979 (Box 95, Folder 1069)
  - Yale University School of Nursing and Connecticut Mental Health Center, "An Institution on Psychiatric Nursing", 1967 (Box 95, Folder 1070)
  - Young, John P., "A Method for Allocation of Nursing Personnel to Meet Inpatient Care Needs," Johns Hopkins Hospital, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 1073)
  - Zinser, Elizabeth, et al., A Feasibility Study for the Development of a Graduate Program Leading to the Master of Science Degree in Nursing at the University of North Dakota, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 1074)
- Scrapbooks
  - General, Circa 1927-1986 (Box 133, Folder 1353)
  - General, Circa 1934-1945 (Box 95, Folder 1075)
  - Class of 1931, kept by Helen "Reba" Wersebe, Circa 1931-1997 (Box 95, Folder 1076)
  - Class of 1931, reunion photographs, Circa 1941, 1966-1981 (Box 133, Folder 1354)
  - Class of 1936, Circa 1930s-1981 (Box 133, Folder 1355)
  - Class of 1938, compiled for 45th class reunion in 1983, books I and II, Circa 1960s-1983 (Box 96, Folder 1077-1078)
  - Class of 1951, gift of Justine Glassman, Circa 1948-1996 (Box 133, Folder 1356-1357)
  - Class of 1951, gift of Justine Glassman, Circa 1990s-2001 (Box 96, Folder 1079)
  - Family pictures
    - Class of 1943, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 97, Folder 1080)
    - Class of 1944, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 97, Folder 1081-1082)
    - Class of 1945, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 98, Folder 1083)
    - Class of 1945W, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 98, Folder 1084)
    - Class of 1946, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 98, Folder 1085)
    - Class of 1946, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 99, Folder 1086-1087)
    - Class of 1946W, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 99, Folder 1088-1089)
    - Class of 1947, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 100, Folder 1090-1091)
    - Class of 1947, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 101, Folder 1092)
    - Class of 1947W, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 101, Folder 1093)
    - Class of 1948, Circa 1940s-1970s (Box 102, Folder 1094-1095)
    - Class of 1949, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 103, Folder 1096)
    - Class of 1950, Circa 1940s -1960s (Box 103, Folder 1097)
    - Class of 1951, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 104, Folder 1098-1099)
    - Class of 1952, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 1100)
    - Class of 1953, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 105, Folder 1101-1102)
    - Class of 1954, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 106, Folder 1103-1104)
    - Class of 1955, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 106, Folder 1105)
    - Class of 1956, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 107, Folder 1106)
    - Class of 1957, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 107, Folder 1107)
    - Class of 1958, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 107, Folder 1108)
    - Students in advanced programs, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 108, Folder 1109)
  - Ogden, Ruth Patterson, Circa 1934-1942 (Box 133, Folder 1358)
  - "Yale University School of Nursing", 1932 (Box 145)
- Special Collection
  - Archives inventory, Circa 1990s (Box 109, Folder 1110)
  - Database, organization of the collection, Circa 1991 (Box 109, Folder 1111)
  - Visitors and request for Annie Goodrich materials, Circa 1996-2007 (Box 109, Folder 1112)
- Staff, photographs, Circa 1976-2003 (Box 109, Folder 1113-1115)
- Student Affairs Office
  - Negatives, proof sheets, and photographs
    - General, Circa 1928-1990s, and undated (Box 109, Folder 1116-1120)
    - General, Circa 1980s-1990s (Box 110, Folder 1121-1134)
      - Oversize, Circa 1980-1981, 1987-1989, undated (Box 143, Folder 1406-1407)
    - Faculty, Circa 1998-1999 (Box 110, Folder 1135)
  - Photographic assignments, Nursing School (includes negatives and proof sheets)
    - General, Circa 1978-1983 (Box 110, Folder 1136-1140)
    - General, Circa 1986-1988 (Box 111, Folder 1141-1142)
    - Alumnae/i Weekend, Circa 1991-1992 (Box 111, Folder 1143-1144)
    - Beckton-Dickinson Award (nursing research fellowship), Circa 1989-1991 (Box 111, Folder 1145)
    - Brochure, Circa 1976-1977 (Box 111, Folder 1146)
    - Capital Campaign and Yale University School of Nursing 1993-1994 Bulletin (Box 111, Folder 1147)
    - Class of 1978 - Class of 1980, Circa 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 1148-1150)
    - Class of 1984 - Class of 1989, Circa 1984-1988 (Box 111, Folder 1151-1157)
    - Class of 1990 - Class of 1993, Circa 1989-1992 (Box 112, Folder 1158-1162)
    - Dedication, Circa 1977-1978 (Box 112, Folder 1163)
      - Oversize (Box 143, Folder 1408)
    - Diers, Donna, reception, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 1164)
    - Exhibit in Cushing Rotunda, Circa 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1165)
    - Exhibit, ribbon cutting ceremony, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 1166)
    - Faculty individuals (Linda Lewandowski, Susan Van Cleve, and Janyce Dyer), Circa 1991-1992 (Box 112, Folder 1167)
    - Faculty portraits (Diers, Schilling, Wacker), Circa 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1168)
    - Graduate program, first year students in 1974, Circa 1974 (Box 112, Folder 1169)
    - Krauss, Judith B., announcement as seventh dean, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 1170)
    - Midwifery program, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 1171)
    - Printed material, Circa 1986-1987 (Box 112, Folder 1172)
    - Publications, photographs for, Circa 1990 (Box 112, Folder 1173)
    - Serafinowicz, L., portrait, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 1174)
    - Students, group of 28, Circa 1991 (Box 112, Folder 1175)
    - Visitors
    - Yale Center for Nursing Innovations, Circa 1985 (Box 112, Folder 1178)
    - Yale Nurse, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 1179)
- Student life
  - "The Ivy Drip," student newsletter, 1979 and undated (Box 113, Folder 1180)
  - Recreation
    - Photographs, Circa 1933-1954 (Box 113, Folder 1181)
    - Recordings, audiovisual
      - "Bixler years", 1939; 1 (Reel 208)
        From container: Movies of Class of 1941 picnic in June 1939; picnic for Class of 1942 in fall of 1939 at cottage; and senior (Class of 1939) demonstration for taking blood. [Film] taken by A. Marcella Brown, Class of 1941.
      - Copy of "Bixler years," circa 1939 and "A. Goodrich," circa 1949 films, undated; 1 (Box 209)
      - "Shell and Tiff stayed all night with us at 900 W. 26th Anchorage", 1969 May 3; 1 audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 210)
  - Student Council activities, 1935-1949 (Box 113, Folder 1182)
  - Student handbooks, skit, photograph, Circa 1924-1954, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 1183)
  - Student illness reports, 1937-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1184)
- Students/Alumnae
  - Alumnae information cards
    - Jobs of Nursing School graduates, Circa 1929-1987 (Box 134)
      Restricted until January 1, 2063.
    - Homemakers or inactive alumnae, class of 1926 - class of 1950, Circa 1920s-1960s (Box 135)
      Restricted until January 1, 2046.
    - Homemakers or inactive alumnae, class of 1951 - class of 1958, and miscellaneous information cards, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 136)
      Restricted unitil January 1, 2046.
  - Alumnae updates log, 1926-1958, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 113, Folder 1185-1190)
  - Publications and news, Circa 1992-1995 (Box 113, Folder 1191)
  - Photographs
    - General, Circa 1890-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1192)